I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. Here are the seven pints I ate
this week. We started off with a cake
batter cookie dough Blizzard. This is
the new Superman limited edition
Blizzard at DQ. Had to recreate it. It
looks awesome. Then I moved on to a Ben
& Jerry's recreation, the vanilla pecan
blondie, which apparently is
discontinued, which is a shame because
it was awesome. Then we did another Ben
& Jerry's flavor, dirt cake topped. This
one was highly requested. Vanilla
pudding base with Oreos mixed in topped
with some chocolate sauce and then
another Oreo. Then I did another DQ
recreation. This was the Choco Brownie
Extreme Blizzard, which was a vanilla
base with little brownie pieces and
chocolate fudge pieces mixed in. And
then I did a brown butter banana bread
ice cream. This was a banana base with
grilled chocolate chip mini muffins that
I fried in brown butter. Like, are you
kidding me? Then I wanted something a
little more refreshing, so I did a
frosted lemonade. This is basically just
lemonade with a scoop of protein powder,
a few other additions. I'll post the
recipe in a couple days. And then I
ended off the week with a cake batter
ice cream. This entire pint has 83
calories, which is ridiculous for how
good it